Finding Aid for the Little Theatre of Nashville Guild Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Little Theatre of Nashville Guild Collection
1926-1932
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0262
.08 linear feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains information related to the Little Theatre of Nashville Guild. It includes bylaws, minutes, and financial statements.
- Bylaws
  - n.d.
- Director’s Note
  - ‘The Skin of our Teeth’
- Financial Statements
  - August 13, 1929
  - June 17, 1930
  - October 22, 1931
  - February 10, 1932
- Itemized Costs of Plays
  - Royal Family
  - The Sea Gull
  - The Fourth Wall
  - Dancing Mothers
  - The Guardsman
  - The Front Page
  - The Doll’s House
  - The Queen’s Husband
  - Hay Fever
  - Lilliom
  - On Approval
  - Wild Duck
  - The Racket
  - Candida
  - Her Husband’s Wife
  - Cradle Song
- Membership Subscriptions
  - 1926-27 season
  - 1928-29 season
- Minute Book
  - June 4, 1927 through May 11, 1932
- Newspaper Clipping
  - June 24, 1928
- President’s Report
  - June 18, 1928
  - June 23, 1930